<HelpInfo>
    <!--Use for unit testing-->
    <Entry id="testEntry">
        FooBar
    </Entry>

    <!--
        Block Info
    -->
    <Entry id="worker_menu_info">
        The worker box allows you to change what type of jobs your worker
        will work on! The 4 roles are general, crafter, gardener, and synthesizer.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="controls_message">
        You can move around the world using WASD. You can zoom in and out using
        the Z/X keys or scrolling. When building use left click to place and right click to destroy.
        You can also open the inventory using the E key.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="start_message">
        Congrats on starting your first space station! Check the science box to see your first task. Good Luck!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="wall_info">
        Nothing can pass through walls.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="ice_block_info">
        Space rock appears randomly throughout the world. One can obtain it by using the mine space
        rock tool (in the actions box). Once you have it, you can use the workbench to turn it into
        steel to build walls, metal floors, etc.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="workbench_info">
        The workbench allows you to craft more complex things. To craft, use the manufacture box.
        Once you click craft, a worker will begin to work on that task. Note: The workbench only works
        on craftable things. Dirt/Unobtainium require other machines.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="compressor_info">
        Compressors add oxygen to your space station. Note: The room the compressor is in must be enclosed
        (with walls and floors) or else the oxygen will vent into space.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="sapling_info">
        Saplings need three things to grow: oxygen, dirt, and space.
        Saplings require a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) to grow.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dead_plant_info">
        Dead plants form when plants (saplings, potatoes, etc.) fail to survive
        in their environment. To grow, plants need oxygen (at least 15%) and dirt floors.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dust_collector_info">
        Dust collectors collect dust from the surrounding gasses. It requires 2 PU / T.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="solar_panel_info">
        Solar panels produce a constant rate of 1 PU / T.
    </Entry>

    <!-- Research Item Desc -->
    <Entry id="basic_material_desc">
        Unlocks the basics materials that are needed for space station construction. Start by gathering space rock
        using the mining menu, and then use a workbench to convert the rock into steel. If you ever need help, you
        can check the help info menu (which can be accessed by clicking on a block in the world or in the build menu).
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="basic_botany_desc">
        Once you have set up a small station, you can grow plants for food and resources. Plants require a dirt floor,
        and oxygen to be present to grow. To get oxygen, use the compressor which collects and compresses
        the vacuum of space.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="composting_desc">
        Using the composter, you can compost leaves to create dirt. Place down a composter, and use the
        manufacture menu to select how much dirt to make. A gardener will then place dirt in the composter,
        wait for it to compost, and then pick it up.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="solar_panel_research_desc">
       Solar Panels generate electricity which can be used to power different machines. They produce a constant rate of
        1 PU / T.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="arc_reactor_research_desc">
        The Arc Reactor uses power ingots to produce a large amount of power. Once built it will run forever, producing
        50 PU / T (50x more than a solar panel)!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="synthesizer_research_desc">
        The synthesizer creates new elements using Space Dust. Similar to the composter and the workbench, you can
        use the manufacturing menu to schedule recipes, and then your worker will complete them. However, synthesizing
        will take your workers multiple sessions to complete.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dust_collector_desc">
        Unlocks the Dust Collector, which collects space dust from the vacuum of space. The dust can then be used
        by the synthesizer to create new elements such as power ingots, unobtainium, and woodroot.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="battery_research_desc">
        Unlocks Batteries, which can increase the power capacity of your station.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="woodroot_research_desc">
        Unlocks the woodroot recipe to synthesize woodroot seeds. Woodroot is a powerful plant that grows out of
        parasites within wood particles. The plant takes a long time to grow but provides a lot of food when harvested.
    </Entry>
</HelpInfo>

