<HelpInfo>
    <!--Use for unit testing-->
    <Entry id="testEntry">
        FooBar
    </Entry>

    <!--
        Block Info
    -->
    <Entry id="worker_menu_info">
        The worker box allows you to change what type of jobs your worker
        will work on! The 4 roles are general, crafter, gardener, and synthesizer.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="controls_message">
        You can move around the world using WASD. You can zoom in and out using
        the Z/X keys. When building use left click to place and right click to destroy.
        You can also open the inventory using the E key.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="start_message">
        Congrats on starting your first space station! Check the goals box to see your first task. Good Luck!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="wall_info">
        Nothing can pass through walls.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="ice_block_info">
        Space rock appears randomly throughout the world. One can obtain it by using the mine space
        rock tool (in the actions box). Once you have it, you can use the workbench to turn it into
        steel to build walls, metal floors, etc.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="workbench_info">
        The workbench allows you to craft more complex things. To craft, use the manufacture box.
        Once you click craft, a worker will begin to work on that task. Note: The workbench only works
        on craftable things. Dirt/Unobtainium require other machines.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="compressor_info">
        Compressors add oxygen to your space station. Note: The room the compressor is in must be enclosed
        (with walls and floors) or else the oxygen will vent into space.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="sapling_info">
        Saplings need three things to grow: oxygen, dirt, and space.
        Saplings require a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) to grow.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dead_plant_info">
        Dead plants form when plants (saplings, potatoes, etc.) fail to survive
        in their environment. To grow, plants need oxygen (at least 15%) and dirt floors.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dust_collector_info">
        Dust collectors collect dust from the surrounding gasses. It requires 2 PU / T. To produce power,
        you can build solar panels and you can transfer it via conduits.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="solar_panel_info">
        Solar panels produce a constant rate of 1 PU / T. Power can be transferred using power conduits.
    </Entry>

    <!--
        Goal Descriptors
    -->
    <Entry id="steel_goal_desc">
        Gather steel so that you can start your base.
        You can collect steel by mining space rock. To mine rock, use the mining
        tool in the actions box. Once you have space rock, you can use the workbench,
        to craft steel. \n Reward: 8 Dirt
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="copper_goal_desc">
        Gather copper so that you can build more advanced blocks.
        Similar to steel, you can collect steel by mining space rock and using the workbench
        \n Reward: 8 Dirt
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="potato_goal_1_desc">
        Grow potatoes so that your worker can eat. In order for potatoes to grow, they need to be on a dirt floor and
        they must have oxygen to breath. The oxygen level can be raised by using an air compressor. Note: If the room
        has any gaps in the walls or floors, the oxygen will escape! \n Reward: 8 Dirt
    </Entry>compost
    <Entry id="dirt_goal_desc">
        Using the composter, you can compost leaves to create dirt. Place down a composter, and use the
        manufacture menu to select how much dirt to make. A gardener will then place dirt in the composter,
        wait for it to compost, and then pick it up.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="unobtainium_goal_desc">
        Now that you have space dust, you can use the synthesizer to create unobtainium. Because
        synthesizing takes so long, it will take your workers multiple sessions to synthesize one piece.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="space_dust_goal">
        Space dust is an important substance that can be used to synthesize more complex substances. It can be collected
        by dust collectors, which require power to run. Power can be
        generated using solar panels. \n Reward: 1 Unobtainium
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="power_ingot_goal_desc">
        Power ingots are used for fuel in the arc reactor. Power ingots are created in a similar method to unobtainium.
        Using the synthesizer, workers can convert space dust into new elements!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="arc_reactor_goal_desc">
        Arc Reactors are the most powerful generators ever built. They use power ingots, a rare and complex material, to
        generate immense amounts of power (50 times more energy than a solar panel).
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="chop_trees_goal_desc">
        To collect wood, you can grow trees, and then use the cut tree tool in the actions
        box. Trees need a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) and oxygen to grow.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="woodroot_goal_desc">
        Woodroot is a powerful plant that grows out of parasites within wood. The plant takes a long time to grow, but
        provides a lot of food when harvested. Note: Woodroot requires one piece of woodroot to start growing the plant!
        \n Warning: Your workers will choose to eat woodroot over potatoes so you must plant it before they eat it.
    </Entry>
</HelpInfo>

