<HelpInfo>
    <Entry id="testEntry">
        FooBar
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="worker_menu_info">
        The worker menu allows you to change what type of jobs your worker
        will work on! The 4 roles are general, crafter, gardener, and synthesizer.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="controls_message">
        You can move around the world using WASD. You can zoom in and out using
        the Z/X keys. When building use left click to place and right click to destroy.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="start_message">
        Congrats on starting your first space station! Check the goals menu to see your first task. Good Luck!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="wall_info">
        Nothing can pass through walls.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="ice_block_info">
        Space rock appears randomly throughout the world. One can obtain it by using the mine space
        rock tool (in the actions menu). Once you have it, you can use the workbench to turn it into
        steel to build walls, metal floors, etc.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="workbench_info">
        The workbench allows you to craft more complex things. To craft, use the manufacture menu.
        Once you click craft, a worker will begin to work on that task. Note: The workbench only works
        on craftable things. Dirt/Unobtainium require other machines.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="compressor_info">
        Compressors add oxygen to your space station. Note: The room the compressor is in must be enclosed
        (with walls and floors) or else the oxygen will vent into space.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="sapling_info">
        Saplings need three things to grow: oxygen, dirt, and space.
        Saplings require a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) to grow.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dead_plant_info">
        Dead plants form when plants (saplings, potatoes, etc.) fail to survive
        in their environment. To grow, plants need oxygen (at least 15%) and dirt floors.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="steel_goal_desc">
        Gather steel so that you can start your base.
        You can collect steel by mining space rock. To mine rock, use the mining
        tool in the actions menu. Once you have space rock, you can use the workbench,
        to craft steel.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="copper_goal_desc">
        Gather copper so that you can build more advanced blocks.
        Similar to steel, you can collect steel by mining space rock and using the workbench,
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="potato_goal_1_desc">
        Grow potatoes so that your worker can eat. To grow potatoes,
        you need to place potatoes plants (in the block menu) on a dirt floor. In order for the
        plants to grow, they must have oxygen. To get oxygen, use the compressor block. Note: The room
        must be enclosed (with walls/airlocks and floors) or else the oxygen will escape!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dirt_goal_desc">
        Compost leaves to create 8 bags of dirt. You can use the composter to compost
        leaves. To collect leaves, you can grow trees, and then use the cut tree tool in the actions
        menu. Trees need a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) to grow.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="unobtainium_goal_desc">
        Now that you have space dust, you can use the synthesizer to create unobtainium. Because
        synthesizing takes so long, it will take your workers multiple sessions to synthesize one piece.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="space_dust_goal">
        Using dust collectors, collect one piece of space dust. Eventually, you will be able to use the " +
        "space dust to synthesize unobtainium
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="power_ingot_goal_desc">
        Power ingots are used for fuel in the arc reactor. Power ingots are created in a similar method to unobtainium.
        Using the synthesizer, workers can convert space dust into new elements!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="arc_reactor_goal_desc">
        Arc Reactors are the most powerful generators ever built. They use power ingots, a rare and complex material, to
        generate immense amounts of power (50 times more energy than a solar panel).
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="chop_trees_goal_desc">
        To collect wood, you can grow trees, and then use the cut tree tool in the actions
        menu. Trees need a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) and oxygen to grow.
    </Entry>
</HelpInfo>

