<HelpInfo>
    <!--Use for unit testing-->
    <Entry id="testEntry">
        FooBar
    </Entry>

    <!--
        Block Info
    -->
    <Entry id="worker_menu_info">
        The worker box allows you to change what type of jobs your worker
        will work on! The 4 roles are general, crafter, gardener, and synthesizer.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="controls_message">
        You can move around the world using WASD. You can zoom in and out using
        the Z/X keys. When building use left click to place and right click to destroy.
        You can also open the inventory using the E key.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="start_message">
        Congrats on starting your first space station! Check the goals box to see your first task. Good Luck!
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="wall_info">
        Nothing can pass through walls.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="ice_block_info">
        Space rock appears randomly throughout the world. One can obtain it by using the mine space
        rock tool (in the actions box). Once you have it, you can use the workbench to turn it into
        steel to build walls, metal floors, etc.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="workbench_info">
        The workbench allows you to craft more complex things. To craft, use the manufacture box.
        Once you click craft, a worker will begin to work on that task. Note: The workbench only works
        on craftable things. Dirt/Unobtainium require other machines.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="compressor_info">
        Compressors add oxygen to your space station. Note: The room the compressor is in must be enclosed
        (with walls and floors) or else the oxygen will vent into space.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="sapling_info">
        Saplings need three things to grow: oxygen, dirt, and space.
        Saplings require a 3x3 area (centered on the sapling) to grow.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dead_plant_info">
        Dead plants form when plants (saplings, potatoes, etc.) fail to survive
        in their environment. To grow, plants need oxygen (at least 15%) and dirt floors.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="dust_collector_info">
        Dust collectors collect dust from the surrounding gasses. It requires 2 PU / T. To produce power,
        you can build solar panels and you can transfer it via conduits.
    </Entry>
    <Entry id="solar_panel_info">
        Solar panels produce a constant rate of 1 PU / T. Power can be transferred using power conduits.
    </Entry>
</HelpInfo>

